Andrew Budziszek

Programmer Analyst Intern

(262) 617-6215 | andrew@andrewbudziszek.com | 3070 N Oakland Ave #4, Milwaukee, WI 53211

Summary

My commitment to professional and personal improvement through continued education ensures I can stay current with all of the newest technologies and innovative business methods. My hard-working, self-confident and goal oriented personality along with my passion for software and technology is sure to bring great work and innovation to any workplace. To learn more about me, my skills, and the projects I've worked on, please visit my website at www.AndrewBudzisezk.com.

Experience

Programmer Analyst Intern | Infosoft Group, Inc. | Milwaukee, WI
Assisted IT staff in conceptualizing and designing software programs using VB.NET.
Created and maintained web scraping programs for 500+ companies from across the
United States. Created SQL queries and performed data entry in SQL Server
Management Studio. Created business features used in our internal systems.
Experience with government compliance auditing.

May 2014—March 2015 August 2015-Present

Software Developer Intern | Penrod Software | Milwaukee, WI

Participate in the full product development life cycle of different applications that solve many problems businesses face today. Researching, designing, documenting, and modifying software specifications throughout the production lifecycle. Coding, maintaining and testing software code.

March 2015-June 2015

IT Intern | Milwaukee County IMSD | Milwaukee, WI

Responsible for imaging and deploying over 150 computers for the revamp of Milwaukee County's technology. (Desktop Transformation Project) Experience performing outstation trouble shooting across Milwaukee County.

October 2013-May 2014

Assistant Instructor | Greendale High School | Greendale, WI

Educated students in music performance to compete at a national level. Specialized in

Percussion. Emphasized leadership, integrity, and excellence.

May 2012-August 2013

Education

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science | UW - Milwaukee | Milwaukee, WI

September 2012-Dec. 2016

Dean's Honor List - Fall 2012 to Present